{
    "subject": "resource/Bury_the_Hatchet_(film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Bury the Hatchet is a documentary film directed by Aaron Walker.  The film is a portrait of the Mardi Gras Indians of New Orleans.",
    "human_readable": "The abstract of Bury the Hatchet film is that it is a documentary directed by Aaron Walker, a portrait of Mardi Gras Indians of New Orleans.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8872692584991455,
            "question": "What type of film is 'Bury the Hatchet'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8828700184822083,
            "question": "Who directed 'Bury the Hatchet'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8517137765884399,
            "question": "Is 'Bury the Hatchet' a fictional story or a documentary?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6456735134124756,
            "question": "Can you describe the main theme of 'Bury the Hatchet'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6102803945541382,
            "question": "What subject does 'Bury the Hatchet' focus on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5278657674789429,
            "question": "Where are the Mardi Gras Indians featured in the film from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47982457280158997,
            "question": "What is Aaron Walker known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37507206201553345,
            "question": "What city are the Mardi Gras Indians from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1128358393907547,
            "question": "What holiday tradition is depicted in the film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07727628201246262,
            "question": "What kind of cultural group is featured in the film?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The abstract of Bury the Hatchet film is that it is a documentary directed by Aaron Walker, a portrait of Mardi Gras Indians of New Orleans.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6433_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What holiday tradition is depicted in the film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6433_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What city are the Mardi Gras Indians from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6433_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Aaron Walker known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6433_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6433_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6433_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6433_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6433_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6433_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6433_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6433_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6433_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6433_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6433_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provided contain information about the film Bury the Hatchet, including its director (Aaron C. Walker), a description of its subject matter (Mardi Gras Indians of New Orleans), and credits for music videos directed by Aaron C. Walker that were inspired by or related to the culture portrayed in the film. This suggests that the abstract is accurate according to the provided documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information that supports this statement. They describe \"BURY THE HATCHET\" as a documentary film about the Mardi Gras Indian community in New Orleans, directed by Aaron C. Walker."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}